xconfessions.com 2019-04-07

# Legal - XConfessions – XConfessions

You are allowed to watch any of the movies in the catalogue as many times as you want in a streaming format. Regarding movie downloads, it's limited to 10 downloads per calendar month. The number of available downloads does not accumulate each month. 

‘Cookies’ are small text files that are stored by the browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Safari) on your computer or mobile phone. They allow websites to store things like user preferences. You can think of cookies as providing a ‘memory’ for the website, so that it can recognize you when you come back and respond appropriately. 

Every time someone visits our website, software provided by another organisation generates an ‘anonymous analytics cookie’. These cookies can tell us whether or not you have visited the site before. Your browser will tell us if you have these cookies and, if you don’t, we generate new ones. This allows us to track how many individual users we have, and how often they visit the site. Unless you are signed in to our website, we cannot use these cookies to identify individuals. We use them to gather statistics, for example, the number of visits to a page. If you are logged in, we will also know the details you gave to us for this, such as your username and email address. 

These cookies are used by software which tries to work out what country you are in from the information supplied by your browser when you click on a web page. This cookie is completely anonymous, and we only use it to help target our content – such as whether you see our UK or US home page – and advertising. 

When you register with us, we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and if you are allowed access to a particular service. It also allows us to associate any comments you post with your username. If you have not selected ‘keep me signed in’, your cookies get deleted when you either close your browser or shut down your computer. While you are signed into either of the sites, we combine information from your registration cookies with analytics cookies, which we could use to identify which pages you have seen on Erika Lust’s websites. 

On some pages of our website, other organisations may also set their own anonymous cookies. They do this to track the success of their application, or to customise the application for you. Because of how cookies work, our website cannot access these cookies, nor can the other organisation access the data in cookies we use on our website. For example, when you share a page or post using a social-media sharing button (for example, Facebook) the social network that has created the button will record that you have done this. 

#### Privacy policy – Lust Productions SL

This privacy policy has been created to help those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. We recently updated our Privacy Policy to clarify how we protect your personal information in keeping with the EU’s new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

We promise to keep your data safe and secure.

In brief, here is an explanation of why we need it and how we use it.

##### Your happiness is our No.1 Priority

We use your data to create the best experience you can have online while you are shopping with us - and in the emails you receive from us.

##### We take your data seriously

We’ll protect your data by using the services of expert data security suppliers.

##### We won’t spam you

You decide what and how you hear from us by setting your preferences. You can opt-out any time you want. And with specific tags, we make sure you are not receiving emails from several automations at the same time, but only information most relevant to your needs and preferences.

##### We will not keep your data for the sake of it

If we don’t need it, we will delete it.

##### We take your privacy seriously

At Lust Productions SL, we care greatly about our customers. We understand your data is precious and needs to be treated with the utmost respect and privacy. In this page, we are going to walk you through why and how we collect private data, how we use it, and your rights.

##### What will you find on this page?

  * How we use your information
  * Sharing your information
  * Marketing messages
  * Keeping your information
  * Your rights
  * Changes to how we protect your privacy
  * How to contact us

##### How we use your information

We use your information in a number of different ways — what we do depends on the information. The tables below set this out in detail, showing what we do, and why we do it.

##### **_1 - What we collect when you use our website, even if you do not subscribe to our mailing list_**

**Your name and contact details**

**How we use your name & contact details (Email, username) ** | **Why?**  
---|---  
Sending you service messages by email. | We’ve got to do this to perform our contract with you (so you can have a transaction confirmation and a link to your membership).  
Fraud prevention and detection. | To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Lust Productions SL.  
  
**Your payment information**

This means the payment method you chose and if it was a card, the last numbers and the expiry date, and the billing address. We do not keep the full number, the CCV.

**How we use your payment information** | **Why?**  
---|---  
Take payment, and give refunds. | We’ve got to do this to perform our contract with you.  
Fraud prevention and detection. | To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Lust Production SL.  
  
##### **_2 - What we collect when you browse our website_**

**Information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website**

Information you give us when you browse our site, including your IP address and device type and, if you choose to share it with us, your location data, as well as how you use our website. We collect this via cookies, but we do not have access to your name and personal details via this technology.

**How we use information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website and app** | **Why?**  
---|---  
Improve our website and set default options for you (such as language and currency). | To give you the best possible shopping experience.  
Protect our website. | To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Lust Production SL.  
  
##### **_3 - What we collect when you sign up to our mailing list_**

**Your name and contact details**

**How we use your name & contact details (email)** | **Why?**  
---|---  
To send you emails and personalize it for you. | To send you emails after you’ve signed up to our mailing list, we really need your email! And if you have given us your name, we like to send emails that do not feel anonymous!  
  
**Your history with our mailing list**

Where and when you have signed-up, in which language, what email campaigns we have sent you, which ones you have opened, which ones you have clicked through, and where you are located when you open emails.

Provide relevant content. | When we see you interact more with one specific type of content, we can adjust what we send out to provide you with what you’re interested in. And by knowing in what part of the world you are located, we can send you information about events we do, stores we’re in near you, etc…  
---|---  
Adjust email frequency. | To make sure we don’t spam you, we monitor your engagement with our emails and based on that, adjust what campaign you receive.  
  
**Transactions history and saved items**

What you’ve checked, added to cart or bought on our website, when you bought

**How we use your browsing, add to cart and purchase history** | **Why?**  
---|---  
To understand what you find interesting. | Because we prefer to send you emails about what you seem to find relevant, rather than random information on the content.  
To sell you things. | If you’ve checked or added to cart a product, we can send you more details about it so you can make an educated decision. And if you’ve bought a product, we may have recommendation on product you might like for more pleasure!  
To make sure you’re happy with your purchase. | To ask you at the right time and about the right product, we need to know what and when you’ve bought. We monitor customer satisfaction to improve our product, our manufacturing processes and make sure you are happy with your order!  
Finding out what you, and other customers, like. | So that we can adjust the website content, the emails content and provide you with a more valuable experience.  
  
You don’t have to give us any of this personal information but if you don’t, you may not be able to buy from the site, and you are unlikely to receive our optimal overall customer experience. But that is your choice – and we respect that.

We also anonymize and aggregate personal information (so that it does not identify you) and use it for purposes including testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our site, and developing new products and services. We also share this information with third parties.

##### Sharing your information

**What we DON’T DO:**

We do not, and will not, sell _any_ of your personal data to _any_ third party – including your name, address, email address or credit card information.

**What we DO:**

However, we share your data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of being able to provide our services to you, as set out in this statement:

  * Companies that do things to get your purchases to you, such as payment service or IT companies.
  * Professional service providers, such as marketing agencies, advertising partners and website hosts, who help us run our business.
  * Credit reference agencies, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so we can help tackle fraud.

We may provide third parties with aggregated but anonymized information and analytics about our customers and, before we do so, we will make sure that it does not identify you.

##### Marketing messages

If you signed-up to our mailing list, we will send you marketing messages by email.

**How to stop marketing messages**

You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time.

You can do this:

  * By clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email
  * By contacting[xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom)

Once you do this, we will update your profile to ensure that you don’t receive further marketing messages.

Please note that it might take a few days for all our systems to be updated, so you might get messages from us while we process your request.

Please note as well that stopping marketing messages will not stop service communications (such as order updates or customer care follow-up if you have contacted us).

##### Storing your information

We’ll hold on to your information for as long as you have your account, or as long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with our Customer Care team) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.

If reasonably necessary or required to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions, we may also keep hold of some of your information as required, even after you have closed your account or it is no longer needed to provide the services to you.

##### Your rights

When it comes to your personal information, here are your rights:

  * The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used.
  * The right to access the personal information we hold about you. You can contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).
  * The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you. Simply contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom)
  * The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances. Again, contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).
  * The right to stop direct marketing messages, by unsubscribing. Ask us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).
  * The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider. Ask us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).

If you want to exercise your rights, or just have questions, please contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).

##### Changes to how we Protect Your Privacy

We may change this page from time to time, to reflect how we are processing your data.

If we make significant changes, we will make that clear on the website, or by some other means of contact such as email, so that you are able to review the changes before.

##### How to contact us

If you have any questions regarding your data, please contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).

And also if you have any questions about our products, your order with us or any ticket you’ve created with us, contact us at [xconfessions@erikalustfilms.com](mailto:xconfessions@erikalustfil%6Ds%2Ecom).
